family priorities always came first for
Mr Sharma which is why his retirement
planning took a back seat at age 59 he
is yet to plan for his retirement will
he succeed in enjoying a happy
retirement while he receives return of
premiums the answer is yes
starting late doesn't always mean a
compromise retirement he can still
continue to enjoy the lifestyle he is
accustomed to with icic approved subtle
Pension Plan life annuity with return of
hundred percent of purchase price ROP
with a single premium commitment of 25
lakh rupees he will be eligible for a
guaranteed annual pension of 1.71 lakh
rupees for life
on his demise his son nominee will
receive hundred percent of the initial
purchase price that is 25 lakh rupees
thus creating a legacy for his
by investing in ICICI Pro subtle Pension
Plan Mr Sharma has done his bit in
securing his Golden Ears he can be sure
because his retirement is backed by
ICICI Prudential life insurance an
insurance company that comes with a
solvency ratio of 204.5 percent here are
more reasons why you should choose icic
approved subtle pension plan plan your
retirement now from the comfort of your
home without video calling assistance
buy online and get one percent extra
pension buy online at
www.icicaprullife.com ICICI Pro subtle
Pension Plan helps you retire they
figure
[Music]
thank you